<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Press Information Bureau </title>
<description>Press Information Bureau</description>
<copyright>Copyright 2009 - 2020 . All rights reserved.</copyright>
<item>
<title>PM to visit UT of Dadra and Nagar Haveli and Daman and Diu, and Gujarat on 7th - 8th March</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108964</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Text of PM’s address at Republic Plenary Summit 2025</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108962</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>MeitY launches AIKosha, a secured platform that provides a repository of datasets, models and use cases to enable AI innovation. It also features AI sandbox capabilities through an integrated development environment along with tools and tutorials.</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108961</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Prime Minister Shri Narendra Modi addresses Republic Plenary Summit 2025</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108955</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>National Debate Needed To Address The Shift From Democracy To 'Emocracy'—Emotion-Driven Policies Threaten Good Governance, Says VP</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108956</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Union Minister Hardeep S Puri inaugurates PNGRB’s new office premises at World Trade Center, Nauroji Nagar</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108953</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dr. Mansukh Mandaviya Inaugurates Office Complex of Zonal Office Telangana and Regional Office, Banjara Hills in Hyderabad </title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108952</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dr. Mansukh Mandaviya Inaugurates Office Complex of Zonal Office Telangana and Regional Office, Banjara Hills in Hyderabad </title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108965</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>DIALOGUE, COOPERATION AND MUTUAL UNDERSTANDING ARE THE KEYS IN AN INCREASINGLY INTERCONNECTED WORLD FOR RESOLVING CONFLICTS AND FOSTERING GLOBAL HARMONY: LOK SABHA SPEAKER</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108931</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Central Electricity Authority to Honor frontline workforce of the Power Sector at Fifth Edition of Lineman Diwas on March 4, 2025</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108918</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Consultation Meet with Industry associations for ‘Engaging Dialogue on Entity Locker’ held at MeitY</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108912</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>INDIAN YOUTH WILL PIONEER INNOVATION AND RESEARCH ON GLOBAL STAGE: LOK SABHA SPEAKER</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108913</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dr. Jitendra Singh Flags Off CSIR’s E-Tractor roadshow from Jammu, to ahead for Kanyakumari , Covering the entire country:</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108906</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nitin Gadkari highlights on immediate need for improved road safety measures</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108902</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Union Minister Dr. Jitendra Singh says, while India’s Bioeconomy grew more than 10 times in last 10 years, the biotech potential of Himalayan territories, particularly their agri-biotech potential, remains still under-explored.</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108904</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Empowering Women in the Mining Sector: A Pivotal Event Celebrating Inclusivity and Leadership</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108900</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>“The vision of Investment in People stands on three pillars – Education, Skill and Healthcare” - Shri Narendra Modi</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108876</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Department Of Administrative Reforms And Public Grievances Organized A Virtual Round Table Webinar ‘Women In Civil Services” On 06.03.2025 To Commemorate International Women’s Day 2025</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108867</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Jan Aushadhi Diwas 2025</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108862</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>PM chairs a high-level meeting to review the progress of Cooperative sector</title>
<link>https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=2108847</link>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
